// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q025: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'After obtaining estimates from several design firms, it proved too ------ to restore that historic building.',
      choices: ['cost', 'costly', 'costs', 'costing'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['costly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Average temperatures in Vancouver in May were ------ low compared to a normal year.',
      choices: ['closely', 'shortly', 'anonymously', 'relatively'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['relatively'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The CEO ------ employees by providing a detailed explanation of the situation regarding the merger with Zell Printing Company.',
      choices: ['itemized', 'distributed', 'reassured', 'launched'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['reassured'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The use of social media advertising has ------ increased the number of inquiries about new products.',
      choices: ['significantly', 'significance', 'most significant', 'significant'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['significantly'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Training was provided to customer support staff to ------ replies to inquiries.',
      choices: ['host', 'expedite', 'found', 'remodel'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['expedite'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'While Ms. Hernandez’s study was on the consumption habits of the younger generation, ------ was on the behavioral patterns of the elderly.',
      choices: ['I', 'myself', 'me', 'mine'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['mine'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: '------ its unique technology, Lederer Systems has maintained its position as an industry leader for many years.',
      choices: ['Nevertheless', 'Unless', 'Consequently', 'Thanks to'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['to'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Margaret Allen received the JDI Award ------ outstanding achievements in new drug development.',
      choices: ['into', 'for', 'except', 'at'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['for'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'After today’s leadership training, please fill out the ------ located on the desk in the back of the room and submit it next time.',
      choices: ['regulation', 'architect', 'exhibition', 'questionnaire'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['questionnaire'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The audio equipment in conference room 103 was out of order, so conference room 201 was used ------.',
      choices: ['respectively', 'beforehand', 'instead', 'consistently'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['instead'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}